formsbirds.com 2019-04-05

# Formsbirds Privacy Policy

Your privacy is of great concern to us, and this policy describes what information we collect and how it is used. Please read this notice very carefully.

### Information Collection and Use

In some cases, we may automatically receive and record non-personal identification information on our server logs from your browser including the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. The information would be used to help us know how best to tailor our content to your interests. Formsbirds will never leak this non-personal identification information to any Third Party Websites without your permission.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Formsbirds may use cookies to help identify and track visitors, their usage of our sites, and their website access preferences. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can change its settings before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.

### Advertising

Ads appearing on our sites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Changes to this privacy policy

We reserve the right to modify this policy at any time. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about our efforts to protect the personal information we collect. However, this policy will remain in effect until a new policy is upgraded on this website.

### Security

All non-personally-identifying information, potentially personally-identifying and personally identifying-information described in this policy is stored on restricted database servers.

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our site, please contact us at .
